Contact

zimmerman.lucas@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lucas-zimmerman-7721a5120 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Inventory Management Process Improvement Manufacturing

Lucas Zimmerman

Software Developer Engineer in Test II at Mastercard Greater St. Louis

Summary

Successful Test Automation Engineer. Experienced in designing and maintaining frameworks to increase test efficiency and accuracy. Excellent analytical skills. A dedicated team member who strongly communicates and contributes to delivering an optimal product in an agile environment.

Experience

Mastercard Software Developer Engineer in Test II January 2020 - Present (2 years 6 months) Greater St. Louis Area

ERT

Software Developer In Test December 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months) Greater St. Louis Area

Biomedical Systems
Software Quality Assurance Tester
September 2014 - December 2017 (3 years 4 months)
Greater St. Louis Area

Manual and automated testing in an agile setting. Performing quality test based on requirements including white-box and black-box testing. Using tools such as Selenium and MTM to create both automated scripts and manual test cases for regression testing to prove positive or negative results.

Ruby Tuesday Server/ Bartender/ Cook May 2004 - September 2014 (10 years 5 months)

Ran tests on all programs written (3 languages) to find discrepancies in the code

- •Adept at running tests to validate code and uncover problems
- •Review requirements to stay within scope

- •Plan the steps to ensure functionality of the programs I created
- Created the pseudo code and coding the programs
- •Created and maintained detailed logs of any code changes made due to errors discovered in testing
- •Demonstrated methodical, detail-oriented and thorough approach to all assignments while adhering to compressed timelines. Complete all assignments on or ahead of schedule.
- •Designed, programmed and tested a shopping App in Cordova for final project in "System Analysis and Design" class; Maintained 100% accuracy on all orders placed over a 10 year period
- •Became an expert at multi-tasking, prioritizing, time management and team work waiting on over 15 tables simultaneously
- •Developed excellent communication skills
- •Providing each customer with the highest level of service

United Pet Group

6 years

Warehouse Receiving Lead/ Production Lead July 2008 - January 2014 (5 years 7 months)

Training new employees and created a team work atmosphere

- •Coordinated daily operations in a warehouse shipping and receiving
- •Maintained the accuracy of materials delivered by vendors, as well as stored items on a daily basis
- Provided job specific assistance as needed
- •Produced manufactured goods based on consumer demand

Warehouse Lead/ Production Lead 2008 - 2014 (6 years)

Receiving Lead/ Production Lead

United States Air Force Aircraft maintenance technician July 1998 - July 2001 (3 years 1 month)

Certificate in aircraft maintenance and engineering

Letter of Appreciation

Education

Saint Charles Community College

Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2014 - 2016)

Saint Charles Community College Associates Degree, Computer Science · (2014 - 2016)